[SINGING] Designing emails can be really tough.
在設計 郵件 可真 難熬。
Client preprocessors can be pretty rough.
客戶端 預處理器 可以是相當 粗糙。
To code email for all their devices,
編寫 電子郵件 的 所有設備 ，
cut the design into many slices.
切 設計 成很多 片。
Mark it up in tables with inline style,
與 內嵌樣式 表 標記 起來 ，
with media queries into one big file.
有 媒體查詢 成一個大文件 。
To win, you'll train and learn the details ??
要贏， 你會 訓練和 學習 的細節 - 。
Unmasking HTML Emails!
揭露 HTML 電子郵件！
Hello, everyone.
大家好。
Welcome to Unmasking HTML Emails.
歡迎 揭露 HTML電子郵件 。
I'm your instructor, Dan Denney,
我是 你的老師 ， 丹 丹尼 ，
and I'll be in your corner as you
我 將會幫助你 ，在你 。
learn how to write HTML and CSS specifically for email clients.
學習如何編寫  專門針對 電子郵件客戶端 的HTML和CSS。
The best way to learn is by doing, so in this course,
最好的學習 方法是 動手做， 所以在這個 課程中，
we're going to take a pre-designed email,
我們將 使用 預先設計的 電子郵件 ，
set up for a large-screen version and a small-screen version
建立 大屏幕 版本和一個 小屏幕版本 。
and write the HTML and CSS necessary for that
並寫入 HTML和 必要 的 CSS。
to display in email clients.
用來在 電子郵件客戶端 來顯示 。
In this particular level,
在這個單元中，
we're going to focus on creating the header for the large-screen version of the email.
我們 要專注於 撰寫郵件在 大屏幕版 的標題。
The skills that you're going to need to complete this course
完成這堂課程，你會需要的技巧有
are a working knowledge of HTML and CSS, CSS media queries,
HTML和CSS ， CSS media queries 的 知識 ，
and we're going to have you use some external resources in order
並且我們 將使用 一些外部 資源。
to complete the code necessary to create this email.
完成 此電子郵件。
At its core, an HTML email is an HTML file.
其核心 ， HTML電子郵件 是一個html 文件。
If any of this code looks unfamiliar,
儘管 代碼 看起來 不友善 ，
we may want to have you first get started
我們 希望 你先 從
by taking Front-end Foundations to learn
前端UI 的基礎 開始上手。
HTML and CSS, or Journey Into Mobile
HTML和CSS ， 或  手機
to learn CSS media queries.
學習 CSS media queries。
The code that we write is viewed in email clients.
我們 寫的代碼  會在 電子郵件客戶端被看見 。
These can be web-based clients, in which you
這些都可以 在 Web的 瀏覽器顯示
would visit a URL, like gmail.com, to access your email in Gmail,
當你瀏覽 一個網址 ， 如 接收Gmail在gmail.com  。
or yahoo.com in order to access your email in Yahoo Mail.
或者是在yahoo.com中的Yahoo Mail接收信件  。
The other type of client are native applications.
其他 類型的客戶端 是 本地應用程序。
One popular version of this for Microsoft operating systems is Microsoft Outlook,
這方面的 在微軟作業系統裡知名的 就是Microsoft Outlook。
and one popular version for iOS clients is the Mailbox application.
在 iOS 客戶端 則是Mailbox App 。
Each of these would be used to access mail for many accounts.
這些程式 被許多人拿來接收信件 。
In modern front-end development, we're
在 現代的 前端開發 ，  。
used to writing code that is viewed in browsers.
我們是在 瀏覽器中查看 代碼。
Those browsers use rendering engines
這些瀏覽器 使用 排版引擎 。
in order to interpret the HTML and CSS that we write.
來 編譯 我們 寫 HTML和CSS 。
Email clients have this same process,
電子郵件客戶端 有這個 同樣的過程 ，
but they have an additional step too.
但 它們 也有一個額外的 步驟 。
They use a preprocessor that will actually change your HTML.
他們使用一個 預處理器 ，這實質上會改變 你的HTML 。
Let's take a look at
讓我們來 看看  。
how preprocessors affect the code that we write.
預處理器 是如何影響 我們 編寫的代碼 。
Their original intention was to protect the operating system
他們的 初衷是為了 保護作業系統 。
from code that could be executed in an application
因為 代碼 可能 在一個應用程序 中執行。
and have harmful effects on the operating system itself.
並且 可能對 作業系統本身 造成有害影響。
Since then, they've added additional responsibilities
從那時起 ， 他們 增加了額外的 責任 。
in that they remove or change our HTML
所以它們刪除或更改你的HTML 。
and CSS, override our styles with their own CSS,
和css ， 用自己本身的CSS覆蓋 我們的 styles  ，
change the entire document structure for web-based clients,
改變整個 在web客戶端的文檔結構。
and remove any and all JavaScript.
並刪除 任何或所有 的JavaScript。
So you're not going to be writing any JavaScript
所以你 無法 寫入 任何JavaScript 。
for an HTML email anytime soon.
在一份 HTML 電子郵件 。
Gmail has the most aggressive preprocessor of all.
Gmail 是 最激進 的 預處理 。
This is unfortunate, because it's
這是不幸的 ，
because it's one of the most popular email clients out there.
因為它是最 流行的 電子郵件客戶端  。
The combination of its popularity
因為他的知名度 和
and its preprocessing affect how we
它的 預處理 影響了我們
have to write our HTML and CSS.
寫出來的HTML和CSS 。
Let's take a look at specifically
讓我們 來看看 具體上
what Gmail's preprocessor does.
Gmail的 預處理器 做了啥事。
First off, it removes any link tags.
首先 ，它會刪除 任何 link 標籤。
This means that any external style sheets in which we
這意味著任一個外部的 style 。
have code would be removed.
都會被刪除。
It also overrides our styles with its own version of CSS,
它也改寫我們 的styles 成為它的CSS 版本 ，
and then it changes the entire document structure.
然後 它改變了 整個 文檔結構。
Finally ...and this is the most harmful to our code ....
最後 - 這是對我們程式最糟糕的一項----
it removes style tags.
它會刪除 style 標籤 。
This means that we can't write CSS in an external style sheet.
這意味著我們 不能 在外部 style 上寫 CSS。
We also can't lump together CSS properties in a style tag
我們也無法使用 CSS 屬性 的 style 標籤。
to apply to our HTML elements.
在HTML元素上。
So now let's go back to our base HTML
所以現在 ，讓我們 回到我們的 基本HTML 。
and start adding some content.
並開始增加 一些內容 。
First off, we're going to add the image for the stars.
首先 ， 我們要 加入星星的圖片 。
One thing to note is that we're using
有一點要注意 的是，我們 使用的是 。
an absolute URL for the image.
一個絕對路徑的圖片 。
Any time that we're adding an image to an HTML email,
任何時候，我們 要添加 HTML電子郵件 的圖片 ，
we need to use an absolute URL.
都需要 使用絕對路徑 。
This image needs to be stored on a server and accessible,
這個 圖像需要被存儲在可被讀取的服務器上 ，
and we will reference it using an absolute path.
我們將 使用絕對路徑 來引用它 。
This is one big difference between email HTML and website
這是 HTML 的電子郵件 和網站 之間的一個 很大的區別。
HTML.
HTML。
All of the images that we're going to use in our example email will have an absolute URL.
所有我們將在郵件中使用的圖片，都需要有絕對路徑
This is a lot of code to look at,
這是很多程式碼 ，
so we're going to abbreviate these URLs using a dot, dot,
所以我們用....來省略這些URL，
dot, like this.
像這樣。
Continuing on with our initial markup,
繼續說我們一開始的重點 ，
we're going to add an H1 and a paragraph tag to our email.
我們要添加 H1 和 DIV 到 電子郵件。
Throughout this course, we're going
在整個 過程中， 。
to be writing a lot of code, and it's all
我們將寫大量的 程式碼，
and it's all going to be in one single file.
在單一個文件中 。
In order to keep focus on the part
為了 能夠專注於
that we're working on at the moment,
我們 正在撰寫 的部分 ，
we're going to collapse the code surrounding the areas
我們要 摺疊 部分 我們正在處理的 程式碼。
that we're working on.
You can see here that we've collapsed the opening HTML
你 可以在這裡看到 ，我們已經 展開 。HTML
and the closing HTML so that we can focus on the body.
和 摺疊起來 的HTML ，這樣我們 可以專注於 body 。
If we take our code and view it in Chrome,
如果我們把程式碼放到 Chrome 上瀏覽
we get expected results.
我們得到了 預期的效果 。
This is unstyled HTML, so we're going
這是 unstyled 的 HTML。
to default to Times New Roman for the font family,
預設的字體是 Times New Roman ，
and then we'll have some browser-specific spacing added.
然後 ，我們 將有一些 特定瀏覽器的 間距 增加 。
However, if we view this in Gmail,
但是，如果 在Gmail中，
we see some slight differences.
我們會看到一些細微的差別 。
Gmail is applying a different font
Gmail 採用 不同的字體 。
family and different spacing.
和 不同的間距 。
This is because Gmail's preprocessor has actually
這是因為 Gmail的 預編譯器  。
changed the code that we've written.
改變了 我們 編寫的代碼 。
Let's use the browser developer tools
讓我們使用 瀏覽器的 開發工具 。
to compare how our code is different from the Chrome
比較你的程式碼在。
version and the Gmail version.
Chrome 和 Gmail上。
First off, looking at the Chrome version,首先，來看Chrome 的版本 ，
we can see that our code is as expected.
我們可以看到， 程式碼是 按預期的顯示 。
The only difference is that chrome is adding
唯一的 區別是。
some of its own default styles.
chrome 增加一些它 自己的 設定樣式 。
Continuing on into Gmail, we see that our code
回到Gmail ， 我們看到程式碼 。
is in a very different place than it was before.
和原本的樣子有很大的不同 。
If you look way down the line of divs,
如果你往下看到 divs  ，
we'll find our code towards the bottom.
我們 會發現 程式碼在底部附近。
So what is actually going on with our code here?
我們的程式碼在這裡發生了什麼事？
If we look at that code that was towards the bottom,
如果我們看一下 底部附近的程式碼，
we can see that it resembles the code that we wrote.
我們 可以看到它 類似於 我們 寫的程式碼 。
Our inline styles are there, but they're now applied
我們的inline styles是有的，但他們被套用在
to a div tag instead of a body.
一個 div標籤 ，而不是 body 。
Our image is there, but it's being
我們的圖片是存在的 ，
served from a different location because Gmail wants
但它被移至不同的位置，因為 Gmail的 希望
to use its own caching service.
使用它自己的 緩存(cache)的服務 。
Our H1 and paragraph tags are left alone,
我們的 H1 和段落 標記 不見了 ，
but Gmail's applying CSS to them via its own style sheet.
而 Gmail的 套用了自己的 CSS。
In fact, if we look at the body tag of the Gmail web
事實上 ， 如果我們 看一下 Gmail  的 body標籤
application, we see a lot of code
我們看到 了大量的程式碼
that is no way related to ours.
是和我們沒有相關聯的。
Knowing what preprocessors are capable of,
了解了 預處理器 的作用後，
we need to write our styles in a way that they won't be removed,
我們需要用不會被移除的方式來寫我們的styles。
and that they can counter any styles created
而且它們 要能 對抗 任何
by the preprocessors themselves.
由 預處理程序 產生的 styles 。
In order to do this, we're going to write our styles inline
為了 做到這一點 ， 我們將styles寫成inline styles
to create our email.
來建立電子郵件。
To write inline styles, the first thing
寫 inline styles 的第一件事。
that we're going to do is add a style attribute
我們 要做的 就是添加一個 style 屬性
to our image tag.
給 image 標籤 。
We'll then add CSS properties to give it the look that we want,
我們 加入 CSS屬性 使它成為我們想要的樣子 ，
and finally add a width attribute
最後加入 width屬性 ，
to set it to 600 pixels.
將其設置為 600像素 。
Here, you can see that our star graphic is taking shape.
在這裡 ， 你 可以看到， 我們的星星 圖形 正在形成 。
Next, we'll follow that same process for our H1 tag.
接下來 ， 我們將用一樣的方式來處理H1標籤。
We'll add our style attribute and add properties to it,
我們將加入我們的style屬性，並給它設定屬性，
but the one interesting thing to note
但 有一個 有趣的事情 要注意。
is that, because we can't reference an area of CSS,
是這樣的....因為我們 不能引用 區域 的 CSS，
we have to include any reset styles on every element that we want to reset.
我們 必須包覆任何一項我們想要重置的元素上所有的styles。
We're going to put margin: 0 on this
我們 打算設定 margin:0。
to counter any browser behavior that would
對抗 任何瀏覽器
add spacing to our H1 tag.
增加間距到您的H1標籤。
Our paragraph tag is a combination
我們的 段落標記 是 一個 由
of both of our prior tags in that first we
我們事先 標記中
need to apply container styles, then font styles, and also
所需要套用的樣式，字體樣式和
our reset styles.
我們重置的styles 所組成。
If we view the results of our inline CSS, we find a problem.
如果看 我們的 inline CSS 會發現一個問題 。
We want all three of these elements to be aligned
我們希望 這三個 元件對齊 。
and to have equal widths.
並具有 相等的寬度 。
We can fix this by adding a div around all
我們 加入一個div 解決這個問題 。
of our current content, applying margin: 0 auto to center it,
在目前的區塊中，套用margin: 0，自動居中，
and applying a max width of 600 pixels
並套用 最大寬度為 600 像素 。
so that it never gets bigger than that.
因此 ，它 永遠不會 大於 600px  。
As you can see now, the content is contained
所以 你現在可以看到，
and the container is centered.
內容都置中 。
To clean this up a little more, we
在更深入了解一下， 我們 。
can apply text-align: center to our div
可以將文字 對齊居中 DIV。
and allow that to cascade down to all
並 套用 到 所有 。
of the text inside of it.
它裡面 的文字。
To complete our header, we need to add a background.
完成 我們的 header ， 我們 需要添加一個 background
We want this background to run the full width
我們希望 這個background
of the available space.
可以占滿所有的橫向可用空間。
In order to do that, we're going to wrap
為了 做到這一點，
a div around our current content container,
我們要將 DIV 包住 我們 內容區塊，
and apply a background color and background image to that div.
並套用 背景顏色和 背景圖像 到div中。
So far, we've seen what happens if we take our code and view it
到目前為止 ， 我們已經看到我們的程式碼，
after it has been through Gmail's preprocessor
在經過 Gmail 的 預處理後
and Chrome's rendering engine.
以及 Chrome 的 排版引擎處理 過後 會長什麼樣子  。
Here is an example of viewing our email after it's
這例子 是查看你的電子郵件 當其
been processed by Gmail preprocessor and Firefox's rendering engine.
在通過 Gmail的 預處理 和Firefox 排版引擎 處理。
As we can see, everything looks great.
我們可以看到 ，一切都 看起來不錯。
Now it's your turn to start building an HTML email in the challenges.
現在 輪到你 在【挑戰】中建立 一個HTML Email
Blap beep.
嗶嗶。LOL
Ugh.
啊。LOL